Larry Bogart Papers 2012.0088
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Inventory, undated, 1958-2001
  - Publications, manuscripts, fliers, correspondence, maps, clippings, 1957, 1969-1975, 1977, 1979, 1985-1986, 1988, 1990; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 23)
    Articles and Publications: U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission "News Announcements" (1985); Publications "Watch on the AEC" (1973), "Energy News Digest" (1985), "Nuclear Hazards" (1986), and "Nuclear Opponents" (1988) from the Citizens Energy Council; Manuscript of article "Is More Better?" (no author, no date); Publication "Bulletin: Anti-Pollution League" (1969); Flier "What the Public Must Know about Nuclear Power: Some Important Statements by Scientists and Citizens" from the Women's International Coalition; U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission "News Releases" (1990); Article "Rio Blanco: Who Bears the Costs?" by Dave Hunter (1973); Publication "Utopia or Oblivion: Environmental Action of Colorado;" Article "We CAN Have Power... Without Risking Nuclear Pollution" (no author, no date); Article "Dawning of Solar Energy: A Proposal for an Exhibit" by Elizabeth Ann Kingman (1973); Flier "The Council for Education in the Sciences, Inc.: Organization, Purposes, Activities;" Publication "Nuclear Energy: Promises, Promises" by George L. Weil (1972); Publication "Nuclear Waste: Hanford Single-Shell Tank Leaks Greater than Estimated" (1991); Publication "War Watch" (1991); Article "Stop the Amchitka Blast" (1971); Publication "Stockholm Conference ECO Atomic Reactor Safety Hearings" (1972); Article "Twin Nuclear Plants: Blessing or Curse?" By Elliot Eisenberg and John Schidlovsky; Publication "Preliminary Report on Nuclear Power Plants" by Massachusetts Public Interest Research Group (1974); Publication "Lithopinion: The Graphic Arts and Public Affairs Journal of Local One, Amalgamated Lithographers of America" (1969); Article 'Statements by Springville Radiation Study Group and the Sierra Club" (1974); Article "Catch 24,400 (or, Plutonium is my Favorite Element" by Roger Rapoport (1970); Article "A Sane Solution to the Energy Problem" by John W. Gofman, PhD (1977); Article "Theoretical Possibilities and Consequences of Major Accidents in Large Nuclear Power Plants" by the U.S. Atomic Energy Commission (1957); Publication "Nuclear Energy: as it Relates to the Environment: A Source of Power for the Midland Area" (League of Women Voters, 1971); Article "Life or Death with the Atom" by Ruth Gage-Colby (1970).
    Organizations: Paper Tiger Television; Women's International Coalition to Stop Making Radioactive Waste; Council for Education in the Sciences.
    Nuclear Plants: Hanford; Vermont Yankee.
    Other Items: Correspondence to Larry Bogart (1973); Poster "Nuclear Power Plant Threats to Ohio and Lake Erie" (1975); Map "Note How AEC Fails to Protect Us" (no date).
    Other Topics: Solar Energy; Sen. James Abourezk; Sigurd M. Rascher.]
  - Publications, clippings, fliers, books, posters, 1957, 1963, 1969-1972, 1976, 1978, 1985, 1987-1991, 1994, 1997-1998, 2001; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 24)
    Articles and Publications: Article "Whatever Happened to the Peaceful Atom?" by David E. Lilienthal (1963); Article 'Radiation Standards: Are the Right People Making Decisions?" by Philip M. Boffey (1970); Publication "A Treatise on the Proposed Calvert Cliffs Nuclear Power Plant" by Jess W. Malcolm (1969); Publication "U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Before the Atomic Safety and Licensing Board, in the Matter of Tennessee Valley Authority (Hartsville Nuclear Plant, Units 1A, 1B, 2A and 2B)" (1976); Publication "Environment" magazine "(1970); Publication "Confuse and Deceive: The Great Nuclear Brainwash" (no date); Publication "The Messenger: Environmental/Health Journal" (1990); Article "The Excited Core" by Stig Flodmark and Kjell Davstad; Publication "The Facts about Food Irradiation" by Irene Kock (1988); Publicaiton "Nuclear Waste in Sweden: The Problem is not Solved" by Karl-Inge Ahall, et al. (1988); Article "Behavioral Kinesiology for the Dentist: An Introductory Overview" by John Diamond, M.D. (1978); Article "Nukes in Space: Bush and the New Push for Galactic Warfare" by Karl Grossman (2001); Publication "Remembering Larry Bogart" by the Larry Bogart Memoral Fund (1994); Publication "Energy Efficiency: A New Agenda" by William V. Chandler, et al (1988); Article 'Open Letter to Planet Earth, Solar System, Galaxy Milky Way" by Joy MacNulty (1987); Article "U.N. Environmental Assembly, April 25, 1991, Five Jears After Chernobyl: Remarks by Larry Bogart and Dr. George Wald;" Publication "Nuclear Chronicle" (1991); Flier "Can You Find Your State on this Map? Radioactive Waste Trains and Trucks are Headed Your Way" by Nuclear Information and Resource Service (no date); Article 'Results of a 1997 National Nuclear Waste Transportaion Survey: A Report by James H. Flynn, C.K. Mertz and Paul Slovick" (1998); Book (photocopied) "Deadly Deceit" by Jay Gould (1989).
    Organizations: Citizens Committee for Environmental Concern, Inc.; Chesapeake Bay Foundation; National Committee to Stop Environmental Pollution; New York State Department of Environmental Conservation; Forelaws on Board.
    Nuclear Plants: Hartsville; Indian Point.
    Other Items: Poster for "International Day of Protest to Stop the Militarization of Space" (Oct. 13, 2001); Letter to the editor by Larry Bogart (1991); Flier against Cassini probe from The Progressive Foundation; Stickers, reading "Danger: Radioactive Waste Transport Route."
    Other Topics: Nuclear waste and fuel in space; Sigurd M. Rascher; Transportation of radioactive waste.]
  - Publications, correspondence, fliers, transcripts, 1980-1981, 1984-1987, 1989-1990; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 25)
    Articles and publications: Article "The Rush to License: Money vs. Safety" by Ron Ridenhour (1985); Publication "Leeds and the Bomb" by Leeds City Council (1984); Flier "Introducing the RDX Nuclear DX-1 Geiger Counter;" Publication "Environmental Radioactivity Levels, Browns Ferry Nuclear Plant Annual Report, 1980" by the Tennessee Valley Authority; Publication "Jet Propulsion Laboratory Fact Sheet: Project Galileo;" Publication "National Geographic: A Special Report in the Public Interest: Energy: Facing Up to the Problems, Getting Down to Conclusions" (1981); Publication "An Operator's Guide to Improved Starch Conversion and Fermentation: Making More Fuel Alcohol" by NCat, the National Center for Appropriate Technology (1980); GAO Reports "Uranium Enrichment: Some Impacts of Proposed Legislation on DOE's Program" (1989) and "Nuclear Waste: DOE's Management of Single-Shell Tanks at Hanford, Washington" (1989); Article "Notes on a New England Survival Conference" (1990); Article "Bibliography: The Larry Bogart Library on Nuclear Energy and Related Subjects" (1989); Flier "Convert to Safe Energy: Join the Maryland Nuclear Safety Coalition;" Article "Foods to Protect Your Family (and yourself) from Radiation" by Sara Shannon (1989); Publication "EastWest: The Journal of Natural Health and Living" (1987); Publication "Environmental News" by the New Jersey Department of Environmental Protection (1989); Publication "American Peace Directory, 1984" ed. Melinda Fine and Peter M. Steven; Publication "Critical Mass Energy Bulletin" (1990); Publication "The Defense Monitor," published by the Center for Defense Information (1989); Publication "Nuclear Hazards" from the Citizens Energy Committee (1990); Publication "Serious Problems Continue in the Nuclear Regulatory Commission's Internal Investigations: Report of the Committee on Government Affairs, U.S. Senate" (1989); Publication "We The People" press releases (1989).
    Organizations: Nuclear Information and Resource Service; International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Inc.
    Nuclear Plants: Hanford, Seabrook.
    Other Items: Transcript of "60 Minutes," May 12, 1985; Transcripts of the Statements of Sharon R. Connelly, Victor Stello and Julian S. Greenspun "Before the Subcommittee on General Oversight and Investigations Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs" (Oct. 5, 1989).
    Other Topics: Plutonium use in Spacecraft; Challenger Disaster; Galileo probe; Investigation of flawed nuclear power plants by Stephen B. Conley, Executive Director of We The People, Inc.]
  - Clippings, publications, notes, 1965-1967, 1969-1974, 1978-1979, 1991, 1993; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 26)
    Articles and Publications: Article "Radiation Decisions: Who's in Charge?" by Egan O'Connor; Articles "A Congressional Seminar: A: The History of Erroneous Handling of the Radioactive Hazard Problem in Atomic Energy Development (John W. Gofman) B: A Proposal for a rational Future Protection Policy With Respect to Radioactivity and Other Forms of Pollution (Arthur R. Tamplin)" (1970); Article "Vernon Folks Have Faith in Yankee" (1971); Article 'Electric Power Plants and the Need for Power vs. The Environment" by the Champlain Valley Area League of Women Voters (1970); Publication "Science" (1978); Article "Solar Power: Promising New Developments;" Article "Methanol: A Versatile Fuel for Immediate Use" by T.B. Reed and R.M. Lerner (1973); Article "Nuclear Safeguards: Holes in the Fence" by Robert Gillett (1973); Publication "Resources" (1993); Publication "Clearing the Air: A Layman's Guide to Atmospheric Purity" by Wallace West; Issues of publication "Scientist and Citizen" (1965-1967); U.S. Atomic Energy Commission News Releases; Publication "Atoms & Waste" (formerly "Radwaste Report") (1991).
    Nuclear Plants: Vermont Yankee; Indian Point; Storm King; Connecticut Yankee.
    Other Topics: 1972 Energy Crisis; Nuclear Waste Pollution; Vermont Governor Deane C. Davis; Dams on Connecticut River; Cartoons against nuclear power; Pollution from Vermont Yankee; 1979 Hiroshima Day.]
  - Clippings, publications, 1965, 1967, 1970-1975, 1977, 1980, 1986, 1989-1991; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 27)
    Articles and publications: Publication "Aircraft Radiation Incident April, 1974 and Aircraft Contamination Incident December 1971-January 1972" by John C. Davis, U.S. Atomic Energy Commission (1974); Article "U.N. Environmental Assembly, April 25, 1991, Five Years After Chernobyl" by Larry Bogart and Dr. George Wald; Publication "Fallout on the Freeway: The Hazards of Transporting Radioactive Wastes in Michigan;" Publication "A Pilgrim Report" by Marion Anderson (1974); Publication "ASDA: New York State Atomic and Space Development Authority Anuual Report, April 1, 1967-March 31, 1968;" Article "Defending the Atomic Establishment" by Anna Mayo (1973); Article "Nuclear Power Risks: Challenge to the Credibility of Science" by Bruce L. Welch (1980); Article "In Fairness to Future Generations" by Edith Brown Weiss" (1990); Article "Toward a Nuclear Power Precipice" by Sheldon Novick (1973); Article "Environmental Contamination from Nuclear Reactors" by Malcolm L. Peterson (1965); Publication "Fusion Energy Foundation Newsletter" (1975).
    Organizations: Union of Concerned Scientists; Coalition for Safe Electric Power; New England Coalition on Nuclear Pollution.
    Nuclear Plants: Vermont Yankee; Maine Yankee; Seabrook.
    Other Items: Draft of Chapter 10 of book "Extra-Terrestrial Friends and Foes" (author unknown); Clippings from "Rutland Daily Herald;" Correspondence from Larry Bogart to Sigurd M. Rascher.
    Other Topics: Storage of nuclear waste; Environmental effects of pesticide use; oil in Midwest; Japanese Nuclear ship accident (The Moto).]
  - Clippings, publications, fliers, posters, galley proofs, 1973-1974, 1977, 1979, 1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1991; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 28)
    Articles and publications: Publication from Committee to Bridge the Gap "Fact Sheet: The Galileo's Plutonium;" Publication of Civil Action suit "Florida Coalition for Peace and Justice, et al, Plaintiffs, v. George H.W. Bush et al, Defendants" (Oct. 10, 1989); Article "INterplanetary Exploration: A Challenge for Photovoltaics" by Paul M. Stella; Publication "Scientific Perspectives on the Greenhouse Problem" by George C. Marshall Institute (1989); Article "Nuclear Energy vs. Global Warming" by Robert Backus; Publication "Counter-Point: The Newsletter of the Alliance to Close Indian Point;" Publication "Union of Concerned Scientists Nucleus" (1989); U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission "News Releases" (1990-1991); Publication "The New Abolitionist" newsletter (1989); Publications "Nuclear Opponents" (1985), and "Nuclear Hazards" (1986) from Citizens Energy Council (1985); Publication "Ready or Not: Why You Should be Concerned About the Seabrook Nuclear Power Plant Emergency Response Plan" by Clamshell Alliance; Flier "Risking Our Lives to Raise Money for the Victims of Chernobyl;" Publicaton "Greenpeace Magazine;" Publication "The Natural Rights Center Annual Report, 1991;" Publication "The Nuclear Advocate" (1986) from Americans For Nuclear Energy, Inc.; Article "Plutonium: An Invitation to Disaster" by Gus Speth, Arthur Tamplin and Thomas Cochran (1974); Publication "The Nuclear Resister" (1991); Publication "The National Bulletin" (1991); Publication "War & Peace Digest" (1991); Publication "Critical Mass Journal" (1979); Publication "People & Energy: News of Citizen Action on Energy" (1983); Article "The Death of All Children: A Footnote to the A.B.M. Controversy" by E.J. Sternglass; Article "Karen Silkwood Without Tears" by Nick Thimmesch (1983).
    Organizations: Natural Resources Defense Council; Citizens Energy Council; Americans For Nuclear Energy.
    Nuclear Plants: Indian Point; Trojan (Oregon); Seabrook.
    Other Items: Galley proofs of "Nuclear Energy Policy: A Reference Handbook" by Earl R. Kruschke and Byron M. Jackson (1989); Poster "I Was the Only Victim of Three Mile Island" (1979), about Dr. Edward Teller.
    Other Topics: Galileo Probe and spacecraft containing Plutonium; Chernobyl; Tenth Anniversary of Three Mile Island accident (1989).]
  - Publications, correspondence, clippings, 1965, 1969-1972, 1974-1978; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 29)
    Articles and publications: Publication "Public Power Weekly" (1978); Publication "Shut Down Times" by the Trojan Decommissioning Alliance; Article "The Four Big Fears about Nuclear Power" by Ralph E. Lapp (1971); Publication "A Primer on Nuclear Wastes for Governor Carey" by Friends of the Hudson; Article 'The Spiderwort Strategy" by Sadao Ichikawa; Article "The Inexorable Atom" by Joseph Rotblat (1970); Publication "Ecology: The Journal of Cultural Transformation" (1969); National Coal Policy Conference, Inc. Newsletters (1970); Article "Atom-Bomb Proliferation: Business Wave-of-the-Future?" by John W. Gofman and Egan O'Connor (1976); Article "Nuclear Power Kills in France: The Story of Malville, July 1977" by Pierre Radanne; Article "Statistical studies of the Effect of Low-Level Radiation from Nuclear Reactors on Human Health" by Morris H. DeGroot (1971); Publication "The Action Faction" (1977); Atomic Energy Commission "New Releases" (1965); Article "Personnel Radiation Exposure in the Nuclear Power Industry: A Preliminary Study of Standards and Risks" by Gertrude Dixon (1975); Publication "Citizen Alert" (1976); Publication "Granite State Independence" (1976); Publication "The North River Navigator" (1977); Publication "NEL-PIA: Insurance for the Nuclear Industry" (1976); Publication "Telephone Directory: U.S. Atomic Energy Commission" (1970)
    Organizations: Friends of the Hudson: Saugerties Against Nuclear Energy; Peace Information Center; Irish Conservation society; League Against Nuclear Dangers; Environmentalists for Full Employment.
    Nuclear Plants: Sterling; Seabrook; Indian Point.
    Other Topics: Nelson and David Rockefeller (clippings).
    Other Items: Correspondence to Larry Bogart.]
  - Publications, clippings, 1967, 1969-1971,1977-1978, 1985-1986, 1989-1990; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 30)
    Articles and publications: Article "Lessons from Chernobyl: A European Perspective" by Bernd Franke (1986); Publication "Space Energy Newsletter;" Publication "Solarex Current" (1986); Publication "Deadly Deceit: Low Level Radiation, High-Level Cover-Up" by Dr. Jay M. Gould and Benjamin A. Goldman (1990); U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission legal hearing publication: "USNRC In the Matter of Houston Lighting & Power Co. et al. (South Texas Project, Units 1 and 2) Evidentiary Hearing" (1985); Article "California's Revenge: Someday a Major Earthquake will Ravage the U.S.--In the East" by Ann Finkbeiner (1990); U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission "News Releases" (1990); Publication "Vietnam... And Beyond" by David Schoenbrun (1970); Publication "Environmental Action" (1970); Publication "Direct Action for a Nonviolent World" (1969); Article "Can the Cities Survive?" by Whitney North Seymour, Jr.; Publication "Commonweal" (1967); Publication "Technology Review" (1977); Article "Time To Blow the Whistle" by Larry Bogart and Friends of the Hudson (1977).
    Organizations: Independent Citizens Research Fund; Women's International Coalition; Maryland Safe Energy Coalition; Citizens Energy Council; Peace Action Coalition; Friends of the Earth.
    Other Items: Photocopied cartoons on Nuclear Power.
    Other Topics: Solar Power.]
  - Clippings, publications, correspondence, fliers, notes, posters, 1970, 1971-1972, 1974-1979, 1981, 1987, 1989; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 31)
    Articles and publications: Publication "Consumer Affairs Newsletter" (1976); Citizens Energy Council publications "Nuclear Opponents" (1975), "People and Power" (1975), "Watch on the AEC" (1978); Publication "What are the Dangers of Nuclear Power?" by the New York City Sound-Hudson Against Atomic Development (SHAD) Alliance; Publication "Watch on the Hudson" from the Friends of the Hudson (1977); Friends of the Hudson flier "Why Millions of Americans Oppose Nuclear Power Plants;" Article "The Economic Myth of Nuclear Power" by Doglas La Follette (1978); Article "Strontium-90 Levels in the Milk and Diet near Connecticut Nuclear Power Plants" by E.J. Sternglass (1977); Publication "National Wildlife Federation Conservation Report" (1975); Publication "World Federalists USA" (1975); Publication "What We Must Do" by John Platt; U.S. Senate "Congressional Recors" (1975); U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission News Releases (1977); Article "The Plutonium Controversy" by Jonh W. Gofman (1976); Dosimeter Corporation "Nuclear Accesories Catalog" (1977); Publication "On the Watch" by New England Coalition on Nuclear pollution (1978); Publication "Groundswell" newsletter (1978); Article "Energy Gluttony and Overkill" by David R. Inglis (1972); Article "Dig Here for Doomsday (How the People of Hanford Stopped Worrying and Learned to Love Radioactive Garbage)" by Roger Rapoport (1972); Flier "What You Should Know about the Hazards of Nuclear Power" by the Union of Concerned Scientists (1981); Article "The Fallacies of Atomic Energy Commission Reactor Site Criteria with Reference to Shorham, New York and Other Urban Areas" by W.P. Carl; Publication "Rad Wast Campaign Waste Paper" newsletter (1987); Publication "Marketing the Nuclear Nightmare: Profiles of U.S. Exports to Five Countries" (1979).
    Organizations: Energy Awareness Center; Friends of the Hudson; Citizens Energy Council; Citizens Committee for Protection of the Environment; Coalition to End Nuclear Weapons; Nuclear Information and Resource Service.
    Nuclear Plants: Indian Point; Shoreham; Hanford.
    Other Items: Advertisement for "Dr. Peter Beter's Audio Letter; Poster for protest against nuclear power (November 13, 1974); Poster "101 Resons Why the Proposed PASNY Greene County Nuclear Power Plant-Cementon should Not Be Built" by Friends of the Hudson (1971); Correspondence to Larry Bogart (1970); Notebook.
    Other Topics: Nelson Rockefeller; Ralph Nader; Energy Crisis (1971).]
  - Clippings, publications, transcripts, correspondence, fliers, 1962-1965, 1974-1975, 1977, 1980, 1981, 1986, 1988-1989, 1992-1995; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 32)
    Articles and Publications: Publication "The Crab Sheet: News of the Safe Energy Movement from Chesapeake Energy Alliance" (1981); Publication "Palmetto Nuclear Report: A Newsletter of the Palmetto Alliance, Inc." (1981); Transcript "Phillip Agee, former CIA Agent, Interviewed by Tom Snyder, WNBC Channel 4 'Tommorow' Show" (1975); Citizens Energy Council Publications "Energy News Digest" (1981) and "Nuclear Hazards" (1981); U.S. Nuclear Energy Commission "News Releases" (1981); Publication "Energy Conservation Bulletin" (1981); Article "Civil LIberties in a Plutonium Economy" by Russell W. Ayres (1975); Article "The Fifth Horseman of the Apocalypse" by John H. Leonard (1974); Article "What the Government is not Telling You about Low-Level Radiation" by John W. Gofman; Publication "The Flight of KA 007: Evidence of Conspiracy" by R.B. Cutler (1984); Publication "Nuclear Energy: Issues and Answers" by Pennsylvania Power & Light Co. (1973); Publication "Public Power Weekly Newsletter" (1975); Legal publication "Nuclear Regulatory Commission to the Atomic Safety and Licensing Appeal Board in the matter of Tennessee Valley Authority (Watts Bar Nuclear Plant units 1 and 2)" (1977); Publication "World Citizen News" (1993); Article "Birth Weight and Infant Mortality Changes in Massachusetts Following Releases from the Pilgrim Nuclear Power Plant" by E.J. Sternglass; Article "America's Radiation Victioms: The Hidden Files" by Clifford T. Honicker (1989); Flier "Facts about the Nuclear Controversy" (1977); Publication "Health Effects of Nuclear Power and Nuclear Weapons" by Katherine L. Kahn, M.D. (1980); Publication "The New Abolitionist" (1994) Publication "Green Politics" from the Green Party (1994); Publication "Citizen Alert" (1992).
    Organizations: Sara Shannon Health Program; Council for Chemical Education.
    Nuclear Plants: Three Mile Island; Vermont Yankee; Pilgrim; Hanford.
    Other Items: Larry Bogart correspondence, from Council for Chemical Education (1962); Public addresses by Amory B. Lovins; Letter on nuclear plant regulation from Sen. Edward Kennedy to Joy MacNulty (1988).
    Other Topics: Ralph Nader; Correlation of Nuclear power and UFO sightings; 1964-1965 New York World's Fair.]
  - Publications, clippings, correspondence, dummies, legal documents, photographs, manuscripts, 1958, 1961, 1964-1968, 1980, 1985-1989, 1991-1992, 1994-1995; 1.3 Linear feet Foldered (Box 33)
    [Subjects Include:
    Articles and Publications: Publication "Jersey Greens Journal" (1992); Article "Disaster at Church Rock: The Untold Story" by Allan Richards (1980); GAO Report "Department of Energy: The Property Management System at the Rocky Flats Plant is Inadequate" (1994); Articles "Memory and Protein Synthesis" by Bernard W. Agranoff (1967), "Taste Receptors" by Edward S. Hodgson (1961), and "The Principle of Uncertainty" by Gorge Gamow (1958), reprinted from Scientific American; Flier on "WISE: World Information Service on Energy" (1986); Publication "On the Watch" (1988); Publication "The Nuclear Congress: How Congress Voted On Nuclear Power Issues: 1986-1988" by Rolf B. Hyllseth, published by "Public Citizen" (1988); Publication "Restoration and Power: Creative Conservation at Cornwall-on-Hudson," published by Con Edison; Manuscript of "Every Person's Little Book of Plutonium" by Stanley Berne (1991); Publication "Save Our Nation," by the Anti-Pollution League (1968).
    Organizations: International Conference on Seafood Irradiation; Scenic Hudson Preservation Conference; Council for Education in the Sciences, Inc.; General Electric Stockholders' Alliance Against Nuclear Power; Citizens Energy Council.
    Nuclear Plants: Maine Yankee; Seabrook; Storm King.